[Episode 15] Yes, this is Galchi's house.
Galchi, it's Uncle.
Uncle, where are you? Where are you at?
Stand up. We have to hurry and go home.
Somewhere far.
Just some place far.
Mom!
I'm healthy and doing well, so don't worry.
I'm doing very well. I'm calling so you won't worry.
Let's hurry home.
It's Eunchae.
Eunchae is in front of our house, Uncle.
Hi.
Where are you going? Where are you going?
Eunchae is still sitting in front of our house, Uncle.
Eunchae.
Is Eunchae still there?
Whoa, it's pretty.
Yes, Eunchae is still here.
Is Eunchae still there?
Galchi, is Eunchae still there? She's not leaving?
Eunchae?
What is wrong, Yun? Huh?
Why aren't you taking your shots and medication?
What is wrong, Yun?
Why are you acting like this?
Why are you refusing your shots and medication? Why?
Do you want to die like this?
Yun, you can't do this.
You can't do this, son. Okay?
I don't know why you are doing this,
but did I do something wrong?
I beg of you.
Please get the shots, and take the medicine.
Please, son?
Do you really want to see your mother die?
Should I just die in front of you? Should I die?
Seriously, what is the problem?
Is it because Muhyeok disappeared? Huh?
What does Muhyeok have anything
to do with you, really?
You said you weren't going to take his heart anyway!
In all honesty, whether he lives
or dies has nothing to do with you!
Why do you care so much?
Yun?
Hey, hey!
I'm sorry, Yun. Are you okay?
Yun, I beg of you.
Seriously, I'll get down on my knees and beg.
If there's something that I did
wrong, you must forgive me.
From now on, I'll do whatever you ask,
everything you tell me to do.
So let's get the shots, take the pills and live.
Yun, let's live and see what will come next.
Hey, Yun.
Yun?
Nurse? Nurse?
Galchi, is Eunchae still there?
Because Eunchae called so many times,
I have no battery left.
Eunchae must know that you are with me.
I don't think she'd misunderstand or
be sad that you ran away with me.
I think she knows why you left.
You left so it wouldn't be hard on her, right?
How painful.
Your love brings tears to my eyes.
But aren't you punishing me a little too harshly?
Because I took love for granted,
this is the treatment I get?
Galchi, is my Eunchae still there?
Eat this, Eunchae. What if you faint from hunger?
It's okay. I won't faint.
Until uncle comes, I'll be fine.
Don't worry.
Have some porridge. I special-ordered it.
Did you know that you haven't even
had a single sip of water here?
What are you planning to do?
Are you trying to end it all here?
[Song Eunchae]
Galchi, is our stupid Eunchae still there?
May I have a ticket to Seoul?
Whatever flight is next available.
I followed Cha Muhyeok around
because I was interested in him.
That's all.
Minju.
To me, love is just a game. Like Starcraft.
I lost that game.
Cha Muhyeok.
Whether you'll kill him, or save him, he's yours.
How could you come to such a great place without me?
It's not good to be so selfish, Mister.
Mister.
Go home. Go.
No.
I don't want to see you.
That's why I ran away. Why'd you follow me here?
I don't care what you say. I'm not leaving.
I'm not going to give you up anymore.
Not going, I'm not going.
Go ahead and try. I won't let you out of my sight.
Mister.
Mister. Mister.
I'll take care of Yun, so take her and go home.
Dying isn't such a big deal.
It's a normal part of life.
Everyone dies.
While you're alive,
love like crazy.
Live happily, beautifully, kindly.
That's how to live.
To waste it away like this...
Don't you feel robbed of
the precious time you have left?
Cha Muhyeok, you blockhead.
I know why you keep running from me. You're thinking,
"How sad she'll be, my Blockhead.
It'll be so hard for her."
I know that's why you keep trying to run away.
But, there is something that you don't know.
The ones who get left behind go on no matter what.
It's more sad for the one who is dying.
People who are bound to live
will do anything to do so.
And I'm a blockhead.
I lose things and I forget things easily.
I'm not very smart.
I bet after just a month,
I'll have forgotten all of it.
That one month might be tough,
but after that,
I'll meet my friends and talk. Go out and eat.
Watch funny TV shows and laugh.
I'll be fine again.
So you don't have to worry about me.
The only thing I ask is you don't make me regret.
I don't want to say to myself,
"I wish I'd been kinder to him.
I should have loved him more."
Don't let me regret anything.
Let's have fun, Mister.
Let's not cry. Let's not be sad.
Do your best to happily and joyfully
live with me.
Live with me, Mister.
Okay.
Let's live.
Let's live, Blockhead.
[Pervert]
[Cha Muhyeok, Mister Pervert]
[Song Eunchae the Blockhead]
- Thank you!
- Enjoy!
It looks good, huh?
Here. Ah!
What is it?
Eat it. It's good.
- I don't want it.
- It's good, eat it! Hurry!
Here. Ah!
Good, right?
Why not?
You can't. You're sick.
You're mean.
Instead, eat this. Ah.
Say ah.
Good job.
What is this? Is this for eating, too?
How do you eat this?
Like this.
Like this?
♪ Jingle bells, jingle bells, jingle all the way ♪
Seo-kyeong.
I bought hot buns for you.
Thank you, Grandpa.
Excuse me.
I think I'll be making big bucks soon.
Should I buy you ten truckloads of hot buns?
Really, Grandpa?
Of course!
I'll be making a lot of money
because of you, Seo-kyeong.
Excuse me.
You've been meeting publishing companies, I heard.
News travels fast.
I wrote a book about Audrey.
I've been to several.
I'm looking for the best deal, though.
None of it was Audrey's fault.
It wasn't her doing.
Audrey thinks her children died.
Everything was my doing.
How is that important?
Sir.
Then go tell her now that her children are alive.
Though she'll find out soon enough on her own.
Sir.
I thought this was it for me.
But I think I'll live happily now thanks to you.
I'll be sure to repay my gratitude.
Yun.
Come on. Really, what is wrong with you, Yun?
Is it because of Cha Muhyeok?
Because of him, you're not
taking the shots nor the medicine?
Are you going to die with him?
Is it because you're sorry?
Because you're sorry that your mother left him?
You don't want to go on living selfishly?
Is that why you're doing this?
How did you know?
How did you know Muhyeok is my brother?
No. It's not that song.
Then what could it be?
That also has the word "lay" in it, too.
There is also a song called "Lay By The Ocean."
Beside Mom...
Lay down.
It had the word "mom" in it.
Lay down beside Mom?
Lay down beside Mom.
Oh!
♪ The leaf boat I left is still fresh in my mind ♪
♪ Even as I lay here in my mother's lap ♪
♪ It must still be floating along the pond ♪
♪ Between the blue moon and white clouds ♪
If it hurts, just scream. Let it out.
If it hurts, yell.
Yell out that it hurts.
Are you okay?
Of course I'm okay. Wait out there.
I said I'm fine.
You don't have to look after me like that.
You must've been shocked, right?
Honestly, you were shocked.
Don't remember this.
How I look now. Forget it.
It's embarrassing.
Don't worry.
I'm a pro when it comes to forgetting.
I had a crush on Yun for 20 years but
forgot all of it, just like that.
Don't worry. I'll heroically forget it all for you!
Aren't you coming to bed?
Oh, I will.
You sleep first.
I can't sleep because you're walking around.
Come here.
Are you scared?
You're scared because
I might do something to you, right?
I have some class, you know.
You're going to fall off the bed.
Come closer.
It's okay. I'll just sleep like this.
Why are you so weird?
Are you really my pure-hearted Blockhead?
Then why are you being weird?
Are you really Mister Pervert?
Someone said that
the saddest people in the world are
the ones without fond memories.
It's true. I agree.
I could live all my life
with just one beautiful memory...
With just that memory, I think I would be happy.
Go to sleep.
Pervert.
If you touch me, you're dead.
Fool.
Your eyes.
Your lips.
Nose.
Your handsome face.
Ugly face.
I really appreciate it. Thank you, doctor.
Yeah. I heard.
I heard. I heard everything you and Muhyeok said.
I was right by the door.
Your brother must have wanted
to take everything that you had.
The guy in the car that day...
Was that Muhyeok?
Where's my brother?
You know, right?
Eunchae.
Then is Eunchae...
His feelings for Eunchae were real.
Where is Muhyeok, Minju?
Son, water.
Give me my medicine, Mom.
Okay.
There's a message for you.
[From Muhyeok: Come get Eunchae]
Why? Who is it?
Who is it?
Isn't Korea beautiful?
No matter where I go, I think
Korea is the most beautiful.
Honestly, Korea's way more
beautiful than Australia, right?
If I get reborn, I want to be born in Korea.
You should do the same.
In the next life, be born and raised in Korea.
If you get reborn, get born in Korea
and live here, then...
Mister! Mister!
Mister!
I'm not dead, Blockhead.
You think it's easy for a person to die?
Mister! Mister!
Mister?
Mister!
Mister! Mister!
Eunchae.
Yun.
How did you know I was here?
Did Minju tell you?
Muhyeok told me. He told me to come get you.
Let's go.
Mister! Mister!
Muhyeok is my mom's son.
My mom...
gave birth to and abandoned Muhyeok.
What?
He came for revenge.
He said it was unfair to die alone.
He wanted to take everything I had.
And becoming my manager? Just a part of his scheme.
And so he seduced Minju.
To lead me to such an end was all a part of his plan.
It was all a deliberate part of his plan. All of it!
Liar...
You can have anyone else,
but not Muhyeok!
Is it a really rich family's house?
That's right. I'm a dog.
Not a human being. A dog!
Muhyeok and I are brothers.
My mom gave birth to and abandoned Muhyeok.
Mister! Are you crazy?
What are you doing! Are you crazy, Mister?
Stop it. Stop it!
Did I make it tough for you?
Okay, Mister.
If that's what you want,
I won't put you through hardship.
[I'm sorry, I love you]
Excuse me? How many hours have we been waiting now?
Isn't she coming?
You're going to miss the last flight.
Oh, there she is.
Don't say anything like,
"He had planned to seduce you."
That's not what happened to me.
His feelings for me were real.
[No saved pictures]
I did that because I wanted to live.
Whenever I looked at you, I wanted to live.
Dying keeps making me furious and bitter.
It's not fair.
That's why I did it.
Sorry, Eunchae.
[Deleting photos]
[I'm sorry, I love you]
Yun, where are we going?
Where are we going?
We are going to start now. Please sit down.
What are you doing?
What are you doing right now?
You two are publicly announcing your marriage?
I thought it might be too late if I waited any longer.
I thought I might lose her, so I rushed it.
[Immigration Office]
I'm looking for a person from Australia
named Cha Muhyeok.
Hurry!
What should we eat?
I want spicy rice cakes. Ramen?
How about you, Seo-kyeong?
I want spicy rice cakes and ramen.
Two orders of spicy rice cakes and two ramens, please.
Yes, sir!
- Seo-kyeong!
- Yeah?
- What do you think of this place?
- Huh?
I'll buy this restaurant for you,
so do you want to run it?
What?
The truth is, I'm very rich.
I'll buy you this seaweed roll restaurant.
Don't sell it on the streets freezing your butt off.
Sell it here from now on.
You're going to give this seaweed roll place
to seaweed rolls?
No... Not seaweed rolls,
but this seaweed roll restaurant.
This seaweed roll place is yours.
This seaweed roll place is mine?
It's not mine.
Bibi, Galchi, Uncle, and grandpa are mine.
Seo-kyeong, do you want to be
the owner of this seaweed roll place?
Really?
I'm great at making seaweed rolls!
Seaweed rolls for sale! Rice cakes for sale!
Why are you crying, Galchi?
Are the rice cakes that spicy? Here.
Galchi, why are you crying?
People are going to make fun of you!
Why are you crying?
Don't die, Uncle!
Don't die!
Who said I was going to die?
I know it all. I know it all.
You're going to die.
That's why you're buying us this restaurant!
You don't have to buy us this place! Just don't die!
Don't die! Stay with us, Uncle.
No, it's not like that!
What's wrong?
I'm not eating this.
Don't die.
[Top Star Choi Yun's Official Wedding Announcement]
Excuse me, is anyone home?
Muhyeok?
It's me, Jiyeong.
Do you recognize me?